<idea-plugin>
    <id>dev.maheshbabu11.http-client-plus</id>
    <name>HTTP Client Plus</name>
    <vendor email="mahesh.b.pec@gmail.com" url="https://www.maheshbabu11.dev/">Mahesh Babu</vendor>
    <version>1.0.5</version>
    <idea-version since-build="242" until-build="252.*"/>

    <description><![CDATA[
        HTTP Client Plus provides a Postman-like UI for composing and sending HTTP requests directly inside IntelliJ IDEA.
        Requests are saved as native <code>.http</code> files, making them portable, shareable, and version-controlled.
        <br/><br/>
        <b>Key Features</b>
        <ul>
          <li>Method selector and URL field with an inline Send button.</li>
          <li>Mandatory Name field used as the <code>.http</code> filename and for tracking/updating existing files.</li>
          <li>Params tab with a key–value table that automatically appends to the URL.</li>
          <li>Headers tab with a key–value table.</li>
          <li>Body tab with a Content-Type selector and a compact overflow menu (Beautify JSON).</li>
          <li>Multipart form-data builder with boundary input and parts table (text or file) supporting Content-Type per part.</li>
          <li>For POST requests, automatically adds <code>Content-Type: application/json</code> if missing.</li>
          <li>Each Send saves or updates the <code>.http</code> file; the first Send opens it, later Sends refresh if already open.</li>
          <li>No separate Save/Retry buttons — Send handles persistence only (execution is manual).</li>
        </ul>
        <b>Usage</b>
        <ul>
          <li>Open via <i>Tools → Open HTTP Client Plus</i>.</li>
          <li>Fill in Name, URL, Params/Headers/Body as needed, then click Send to save.</li>
          <li>Run the request manually from the editor with <code>Ctrl+Enter</code>.</li>
          <li>Files are stored under <code>http-client-plus/collections</code> in your project.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>1.0.5</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Added support for Response File saving and viewing within the tool window.</li>
          <li>Fixed an issue where the tool window might not open on the first attempt.</li>
          <li>Improved error handling for file operations.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>1.0.4</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Added support for custom Content-Type headers in multipart form-data requests.</li>
          <li>Improved UI responsiveness when switching between tabs.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>1.0.3</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed a bug where the Params tab did not correctly append parameters to the URL.</li>
          <li>Enhanced validation for the Name field to prevent invalid filenames.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>1.0.2</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Added a Beautify JSON option in the Body tab's overflow menu.</li>
          <li>Improved error messages for failed HTTP requests.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2>1.0.1</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Initial release with core features including method selector, URL field, Params/Headers/Body tabs, and file saving functionality.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="java.xml">com.intellij.modules.java</depends>


    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="HTTP Client Plus"
                    secondary="true"
                    anchor="right"
                    icon="/icons/toolWindow.svg"
                    factoryClass="dev.maheshbabu11.httpclientplus.HttpClientPlusToolWindowFactory"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <action id="dev.maheshbabu11.httpclientplus.OpenAction"
                class="dev.maheshbabu11.httpclientplus.OpenHttpClientPlusAction"
                text="Open HTTP Client Plus"
                description="Open the HTTP Client Plus tool window">
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>
